Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
Please.
Please sit down.
Then let's get started with the meeting.
Please.
The first corner is
Flying self-introductions.
So, I'd like to introduce myself to each of you.
Each of you
Please tell us a little personal information about yourself.
I'd like to ask you to tell us a little personal information about yourselves.
Mr. Amano
Talk without moving the soil.
I will probably ask you to do this.
I understand.
Yes, that's right.
To speak without moving it at all.
It's hard.
We don't understand each other at all.
Thank you very much.
Ms. Aida.
You know, I'm not a fan of people's negativity. I can turn people's negatives into positives.
I can turn them all into positives.
If it says
For example.
I'm worried about the skinny part.
then you can turn it back into a positive.
Some people like that kind of person.
OK.
I understand.
And Mr. Sakai.
Keep talking to Japanese.
Yes, I do.
For example.
I like dogs.
I have a dog too.
I have a miniature pinscher and a
I have a miniature pinscher and a bulldog.
Boss and Ryon are so cute.
They're so cute.
When I'm asked to talk about them
I'd tell them about them.
I always thought they were my favorite dogs.
I can talk quite a bit.
Who, by the way, is nervous right now.
Yes, I am.
But really. But really.
I'm sure you're all nervous.
Of course, I'm sure there's a lot of tension.
I'm sure there's a lot of nervousness on everyone's part.
I think that's what makes you all so lovely.
That way, everyone's cuteness
and your charm will come through.
No matter what happens, it's okay.
We can edit it.
From the viewer's point of view
I have a cute mind.
Don't worry about it.
Let's have fun and be merry!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm nervous
I'm coming in.
Flying 10
I'm so excited!
I'll do my best.
Flying 10.
Good morning.
Good morning
Flying 10
Good morning Best regards
Today is
Our first show
Flying 10's first show
It's going to be recorded.
I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous I can't speak.
I can't keep my mouth shut.
I don't know what to do.
I've been so nervous since the meeting.
Just be your usual self.
"Please do it the same way you always do.
I'll just relax and do my best.
Let's just relax and go for it.
My stomach is growling, so I'm relaxed.
Your stomach's growling?
I'm nervous.
You're nervous.
I'm trying to be formal.
But if we can show our true colors...
I hope we can show our true colors here at Mr. Cool.
I'll do my best.
Let the members greet you.
Good morning.
This is my first variety show. This is my first variety show.
There are a lot of things I don't understand.
but we will all do our best
We will do our best to make the show exciting.
Please take care of us from now on.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Five seconds before the show.
Four, three,
Seino.
Flying JOY!
Here we go. It's Niyari Equal Joy's first Camboree show, Blythe Joy!
I'm Niyari, and I'm the MC. Please give me your best regards.
Please give my best regards.
Mr. Yamamoto, please come forward.
I was born in Osaka Prefecture.
I am 17 years old, and my name is Alice Yamano, aka Alice of 17 years old.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh, simple.
Because it's the simplest thing here.
I am a customer who will ask Minamikawa to make a confession that fits the situation.
Please confess to me.
Ha-ha-ha. Ha-ha-ha.
I see.
No, I don't.
I like you.
Please go out with me.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
How was the recording of your first fanmalley program?
It was a lot of fun and I learned a lot,
I learned a lot, and most of all, I appreciated the warmth of the room.
How was the variety show?
I started by showing off my pinky radish,
She is thick too.
It's true.
But maybe I am thick after all. I might have won.
We unexpectedly found something in common.
If there is anyone else who is thick, please play with me.
The first thing is nervousness.
It's nice to meet you, Mr. Minamikawa,
He helped me a lot,
I think we ended up laughing at the end,
How did you do?
You were so nervous that your voice was shaking at first.
Your voice was shaky.Your voice trembles.
I was shaking when I introduced myself,
At first, everyone was lifting the corners of their mouths.
They kept going up.
It was fun.
Is there anything you think is worth mentioning?
I would like people to see the parts where I put my body on the line,
I'm not good at reckless behavior, but I'm a near-joy,
I'm not good at taking reckless risks, so I'd like to do my best,
I will do my best.
I was told that you were going to do a keru about Mr. Minamikawa,
It had been a long time since I had the feeling of being in a keru,
It made me feel nostalgic.
It was the system.
The system softened me up.
It was fun,
It all happened so fast.
I was really nervous and shaking at first,
When I introduced myself, tears started to well up in my eyes,
Mr. Minamikawa was really kind and helped me a lot,
I was so grateful.
Ai-chan is so great,
Ai-chan shines brightly,
I have great respect for you as a leader.
I still spend every day in rehearsal,
But I still don't know the part of her that I didn't know, But I still didn't know about some of them,
We had a lot of fun participating in the event, and we had a lot of fun,
It was a lot of fun for us to be a part of it,
I am very happy that everyone can know about this girl,
I am very happy to know that you all know about this girl.
Did you see it? Did everyone see it?
Did you see it?
I would love to hear your impressions.
We are looking forward to hearing from you.
Watch this on YouTube,
I'd like to know if there are people who can watch this on YouTube,
If you have any highlights, or anything you would like people to see, please let us know.
I would like to show that I am good at sour food,
I tried my hand at lemons and other sour foods,
I didn't know I was so good at sour food,
I didn't know I was so good at sour food until today,
It was a new discovery for me.
It was amazing.
It's still important.
I'm sour now that I decided to talk about it. Around here.
There were confessions and such.
Yes, there were.
I think there were some scenes that broke the color that we don't usually show,
Even for those who know Nia Joy,
Even those who know Nia Joy for the first time,
I think it will be an opportunity for those who know Nia Joy and those who are new to Nia Joy to learn about the group, I think it will give you a chance to see what kind of group we are,
Please take a look.
So, this is our first kammuni program at Furu-san,
Flying Joy. Please watch it.
Please watch it.